Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: November 13, 2021

The online version is available at

• https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

Residence

Bangkok, Thailand

Phone

+66831225471

GitHub

pitchayakit

Email

☑ pitchayakit.p@gmail.com

Laravel	++++	PHP	++++	SCSS	++++	jQuery	++++	Bootstrap	++++	Tailwind	++++
WordPress	++++	Resful	++++	GIT	++++	SQL	++++	C	++++	AlpineJs	+++
Livewire	+++	VueJs	+++	NodeJs	+++	Linux	+++	Python	++		

Over 5 years of software development career in a variety of companies including startup and digital agency. I graduated with a Master's degree in Network Learning Technology, NCU, Taiwan. I has been working on both back-end and front-end website development. Moreover, I am intersted in IoT and Machine learning. Please get in touch

Professional Experience

Lexicon

2020 - Present

- Managed up Line CRM system
- Managed up CMS using Laravel and WordPress
- Electric search
- Data migration
- Coaching internships in web development and technical support



Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed up to 5 company websites
- Managed up to 2 E-commerce websites
- 1 library website for searching books using Laravel

| WordPress | Laravel |

Empag

2017 - 2018

- Coaching internships in web development and technical support
- Managed up to 4 web content management systems and tasks at a given time
- Collaborate with designer in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the designy
- A Support tool for web scraping and export to excel file

WordPress NodeJs

Onestockhome

Mar 2017 – Sep 2017

• Migration content management system to Ruby on Rail platform

- Developed front-end website using jQuery, Boostrap, HTML and CSS in Ruby on Rail platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improve user interface

Ruby on Rail React

Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML to WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed up to 4 webs content management system and tasks at a given time.
- Collaborate with project manager to develop website, which is beyond own management project

WordPress JQuery

SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework | HTML Canvas | Joomla | OpenCV | MongoDB

Education

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

Additional Experience

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

[IoT] Zenbo] Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control System.

IoT PHP JQuery